Anjali Gupta

Summary

Team player as python developer and client interaction with 3 year experience and also handling teams, who believes in knowledge sharing with a can-do attitude, phenomenal time management skills, and a strong user focus on data science projects

Experience

Python Developer, Denave India Pvt Ltd, NOIDA (June 2019 – Current)

Vertical Prediction

- Create a data from scrapping different website (Linkedin, glassdoor, etc)
- Predict company vertical and sub vertical using company description.
- Training data using BERT model
- Technology used: Scrapy, SQL Server, Python, Pandas, NLP, Pytorch, Pyspark

Beat Plan Optimization

- Automate the daily task allotment for the field user on the basis of previous data
- Scrap store location from different websites.
- Perform Geospatial Analysis on sales and marketing data.
- Analysis on the minimum distance b/w stores at time when seller is on ground.
- Analysis of user and Distributor performance using Regression
- Using Time Series analysis for sales and marketing
- Technology used: SQL Server, Python, Pandas, pattern Analysis, Time Based Analysis, Pyspark, R Studio

Planogram

- · Detect store name from image using object detection method
- · Train the model of different images with its respective name
- Read store name from images using OCR detection.
- Technology Used: Flask, TensorFlow, SQL Server, Python, Pandas, Pyspark

Software Developer, FlixStock, Gurgaon (Feb 2018- June 2019)

Tagging

- Object Detection and Classification of images
- Preparing Dataset to train model by using Pandas and OpenCV.
- Fetches data from website by using Selenium and BeautifulScoup.
- Manage that dataset by using Data Analysis tools Pandas.
- Technology used: Pandas, OpenCV, Python, JavaScript, Shell Scripting,

Mnt

- Tracking files in step by step by using data analysis using Pandas.
- Handing database by using Data Analysis tools and python
- Technology Used: Pandas, OpenCV, Python, JavaScript, Phototshop Scripting, AWS

Certification

- Qualify SNACKDOWN 2016 organized by Codechef.
- Secured 36th Rank in kronothon organized by Kronos.
- Qualified up to 2nd level robotics in IIT Bombay.
- Participated in Digital India hackathon organized by Rajasthan Govt.
- Certified SAFe 5.0 Product Owner and Product Manger

Education

 JSS Academy of Technical Education, Noida, 2014-17

B.Tech in Computer Science with 68%

 Km. Mayawati Govt Girls Polytechnic, 2012- 14

Diploma in CSE with 78.1%

• CBSE, 2010 with 60%

Personal Info

Phone

9899804362

E-mail

Mailme2605@gmail.com

Date of birth

May 26, 1995

Linkedin

https://www.linkedin.com/in/anjali-ag/

GitHub

https://github.com/githubanjali

StackOverflow https://stackoverflow.com/users/9603390/anjali-gupta

Skills

Python, NLP, deep

Learning OpenCV, Pandas,

Django Rest Framework,

MYSQL, Git, Data

Structure. Algorithm, Web-

Crawling, Data Analysis,

TensorFlow, Pytorch,

Flask, Pyspark

Languages

Hindi, English